const data = [
    {
        question: "Grand Central Terminal, Park Avenue, New York is the worldâ€™s",
        options: ["highest railway station", "longest railway station", "largest railway station", "None of the above"],
        correct_option: "largest railway station"
    },
    {
        question: "Exposure to sunlight helps a person improve his health because",
        options: ["resistance power increases", "the infrared light kills bacteria in the body", "the ultraviolet rays convert skin oil into Vitamin D", "the pigment cells in the skin get stimulated and produce a healthy tan"],
        correct_option: "the ultraviolet rays convert skin oil into Vitamin D"
    },
    {
        question: "Where can Coral reefs be found in India?",
        options: ["The Malabar Coast", "Rameshwaram", "Trivandrum", "Mahabalipuram"],
        correct_option: "Rameshwaram"
    },
    {
        question: "The United Nations Organization has its Headquarters at",
        options: ["Bali", "Hague", "New York, USA", "Washington DC"],
        correct_option: "New York, USA"
    },
    {
        question: "Objects at the surface of water can be viewed from a submarine under water by using this instrument.",
        options: ["Stethescope", "Periscope", "Kaleidoscope", "Telescope"],
        correct_option: "Periscope"
    },
    {
        question: "At room temperature, which is the only metal that is in liquid form?",
        options: ["Iron", "Aluminum", "Mercury", "Silver"],
        correct_option: "Silver"
    },
    {
        question: "This scientist is well known for his theory of relativity. Who is he?",
        options: ["Thomas Alva Edison", "Albert Einstein", "Marconi", "James Watt"],
        correct_option: "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
        question: "A Horse walks into a bar- This Book is written by-",
        options: ["Jessica Cohen", "David Grossman", "Dovelah Gee", "Han Kang"],
        correct_option: "David Grossman"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following countries has launched the DAMPE (Dark matter of explore) satellite?",
        options: ["China", "Russia", "Japan", "USA"],
        correct_option: "China"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a nuclear power center?",
        options: ["Narora", "Kota", "Chamera", "Kakrapara"],
        correct_option: "Chamera"
    }

]

export default data;